Guide to the Sterling Lord Papers MSS.058
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series VI: Print Materials, 1950s-2010s; 108 Linear Feet in 108 record cartons.
  - Subseries VI.A: 2016 Accretion
    - Bainbridge, Beryl. Sweet William (Box 305, Folder 1)
    - Baker, Carlos. Ernest Hemingway: A Life Story (Box 305, Folder 2)
    - Baldridge, Letitia. Letitia Baldrige's Coomplete Guide to a Great Social Life (Box 305, Folder 3)
    - Baldrige, Letitia. Letitia Baldrige's Complete Guide to Executive Manners (Box 305, Folder 4)
    - Barnet, Richard J. The Alliance: America-Europe-Japan, Makers of the Postwar World (Box 305, Folder 5)
    - Barnet, Richard J. Real Security: Restoring American Power In a Dangerous Decade (Box 305, Folder 6)
    - Barnet, Richard J. and Ronald E. Mueller. Global Reach: The Power of the Multinational Corporations (Box 305, Folder 7)
    - Barr Jr., Alfred H. Picasso: Fifty Years of His Art (Box 305, Folder 8)
    - Barth, John. Lost in the Funhouse (Box 305, Folder 9)
    - Bass, Jack. Porgy Comes Homes: South Carolina After Three Hundred Years (Box 305, Folder 10)
    - Bass, Jack and Walter DeVries. The Transformation of Southern Politics: Social Change and Political Consequence Since 1945 (Box 305, Folder 11)
    - Baumann, Leslie. The Skin Type Solution (Box 305, Folder 12)
    - Bayh, Marvella. Marvella: A Personal Journey (Box 306, Folder 1)
    - Beach, Edward L. Cold is the Sea (Box 306, Folder 2)
    - Beach, Edward L. Dust on the Sea (Box 306, Folder 3)
    - Beach, Edward L. Scapegoats: A Defense of Kimmel and Short at Peal Harbor (Box 306, Folder 4)
    - Beach, Edward L. The United States Navy (Box 306, Folder 5)
    - Beach, Edward L. The United States Navy: 200 Years (Box 306, Folder 6)
    - Beard, Geoffrey. The Compleat Gentleman (Box 306, Folder 7)
    - Bedford, Sybille. A Compass Error (Box 306, Folder 8)
    - Belli, Melvin M. Melvin Belli: My Life on Trial (Box 306, Folder 9)
    - Belli, Melvin M. with Maurice C. Carroll. Justice in Dallas (Box 306, Folder 10)
    - Bellows, Jim. The Last Editor: How I Saved the New York Times, The Washington Post and the Los Angeles Times From Dullness and Complacency (Box 306, Folder 11)
    - Berenstain, Stan & Jan. ...And Beat Him When He Sneezes (Box 307, Folder 1)
    - Berenstain, Stan & Jan. Are Your Parents For Real? (Box 307, Folder 2)
    - Berenstain, Stan & Jan. Are Your Parents For Real? (Box 307, Folder 2)
    - Berenstain, Stan & Jan. Baby Makes Four (Box 307, Folder 3)
    - Berenstain, Stan & Jan. The Bears' Christmas (Book and Tape) (Box 307, Folder 4)
    - Berenstain, Stan & Jan. The Bear Essentials: Everything Today's Hard-Pressed Parent Needs to Know About Brining Up Happy, Healthy Kids (Box 307, Folder 5)
    - Berenstain, Stan & Jan. Bedside Lover Boy (Box 307, Folder 6)
    - Berenstain, Stan & Jan. Berenstain's Baby Book (Box 307, Folder 7)
    - Berenstain, Stan & Jan. Berenstain's Baby Book (Box 307, Folder 7)
    - Berenstain, Stan & Jan. The Berenstain's Baby Book (Box 307, Folder 8)
    - Berenstain, Stan & Jan. The Berenstain's Baby Book (Box 307, Folder 8)
    - Berenstain, Stan & Jan. The Berenstain Bears: All Year Long! [coloring book with 3 crayons] (Box 307, Folder 9)
    - Berenstain, Stan & Jan. The Berenstain Bears and the Bermuda Triangle (Box 307, Folder 10)
    - Berenstain, Stan & Jan. The Berenstain Bears' Big Book of Science and Nature (Box 307, Folder 11)
    - Berenstain, Stan & Jan. The Berenstain Bears and the Big Date (Box 307, Folder 12)
    - Berenstain, Stan & Jan. The Berenstain Bears and the Big Election (Box 307, Folder 13)
    - Berenstain, Stan & Jan. The Berenstain Bears at Camp Crush (Box 307, Folder 14)
    - Berenstain, Stan & Jan. The Berenstain Bears' Christmas Tree (Box 307, Folder 15)
    - Berenstain, Stan & Jan. The Berenstain Bears' Class Trip (Box 307, Folder 16)
    - Berenstain, Stan & Jan. The Berenstain Bears' Comic Valentine (Box 307, Folder 17)
    - Berenstain, Jan & Mike. The Berenstain Bears' Computer Trouble (Box 307, Folder 18)
    - Berenstain, Stan & Jan. The Berenstain Bears' Count On Numbers Coloring Book [4 copies] (Box 307, Folder 19)
    - Berenstain, Stan & Jan. The Berenstain Bears Go the School (Box 307, Folder 20)
    - Berenstain, Stan & Jan. The Berenstain Bears on Vacation! (Box 307, Folder 21)
    - Berenstain, Stan & Jan. The Berenstain Bears and the Dinosaurs (Box 307, Folder 22)
    - Berenstain, Stan & Jan. The Berenstain Bears and the Eager Beavers [2 copies] (Box 307, Folder 23)
    - Berenstain, Stan & Jan. The Berenstain Bears and the Galloping Ghost (Box 307, Folder 24)
    - Berenstain, Stan & Jan. The Berenstain Bears and the Giddy Grandma (Box 307, Folder 25)
    - Berenstain, Stan & Jan. The Berenstain Bears Go Fly a Kite (Box 307, Folder 26)
    - Berenstain, Mike. The Berenstain Bears: Gone Fishin' (Box 308, Folder 1)
    - Berenstains, The. The Berenstain Bears: The Goofy, Goony Guy (Box 308, Folder 2)
    - Berenstain, Stan & Jan. The Berenstain Bears and the G-Rex Bones (Box 308, Folder 3)
    - Berenstain, Stan & Jan. The Berenstain Bears and the Haunted Hayride (Box 308, Folder 4)
    - Berenstain, Stan & Jan. The Berenstain Bears' Home Sweet Tree (Box 308, Folder 5)
    - Berenstain, Stan & Jan with Mike Berenstain. The Berenstain Bears Learn to Share (Box 308, Folder 6)
    - Berenstain, Stan & Jan. The Berenstain Bears' Life With Papa (Box 308, Folder 7)
    - Berenstain, Stan & Jan. The Berenstain Bears: Lost in Cyberspace (Box 308, Folder 8)
    - Berenstain, Stan & Jan. The Berenstain Bears and the New Girl in Town (Box 308, Folder 9)
    - Berenstain, Stan & Jan. The Berenstain Bears' Nursery Tales (Box 308, Folder 10)
    - Berenstain, Stan & Jan. The Berenstain Bears: On the Job (Box 308, Folder 11)
    - Berenstains, The. The Berenstain Bears: Phenom in the Family (Box 308, Folder 12)
    - Berenstain, Stan & Jan. The Berenstain Bears and Queenie's Crazy Crush (Box 308, Folder 12A)
    - Berenstains, The. The Berenstain Bears: Ride like the Wind (Box 308, Folder 13)
    - Berenstain, Stan & Jan with Mike Berenstain. The Berenstain Bears Save Christmas (Box 308, Folder 14)
    - Berenstain, Stan & Jan with Mike Berenstain. The Berenstain Bears Save Christmas [3 copies] (Box 308, Folder 15)
    - Berenstain, Mike. The Berenstain Bears: Say "I'm Sorry!" (Box 308, Folder 16)
    - Berenstain, Stan & Jan. The Berenstain Bear Scouts Meet Bigpaw (Box 308, Folder 17)
    - Berenstain, Stan & Jan. The Berenstain Bears Scots in Giant Bat Cave (Box 308, Folder 18)
    - Berenstain, Stan & Jan. The Berenstain Bear Scouts and the Humongous Pumpkin (Box 308, Folder 19)
    - Berenstain, Stan & Jan. The Berenstain Bear Scouts and the Run-Amuck Robot [3 copies] (Box 308, Folder 20)
    - Berenstain, Stan & Jan. Los Osos Scouts Berenstain y el Robot Chiflado [4 copies] (Box 308, Folder 20A)
    - Berenstain, Stan & Jan. The Berenstain Bear Scouts and The Runamuck Dogshow (Box 308, Folder 21)
    - Berenstain, Stan & Jan. The Berenstain Bear Scouts and the Sinister Smoke Ring [2 copies shrinkwrapped with a pin] (Box 308, Folder 22)
    - Berenstain, Stan & Jan. The Berenstain Bear Scouts and the Sinister Smoke Ring [Colorado, Illinois, & New York State Editions] (Box 308, Folder 23)
    - Berenstain, Stan & Jan. The Berenstain Bears Shoot the Rapids (Box 308, Folder 24)
    - Berenstain, Stan & Jan. The Berenstain Bears' Soccer Star (Box 308, Folder 25)
    - Berenstain, Stan & Jan with Mike Berenstain. The Berenstain Bears: Storybook Treasury (Box 308, Folder 26)
    - Berenstain, Stan & Jan. The Berenstain Bears' Thanksgiving (Box 308, Folder 27)
    - Berenstains, The. The Berenstain Bears: Too Small for the Team (Box 308, Folder 28)
    - Berenstains, The. The Berenstain Bears: We Like Kites (Box 308, Folder 29)
    - Berenstain, Jan & Mike. The Berenstain Bears: We Love Our Mom (Box 308, Folder 30)
    - Berenstain, Mike. The Berenstain Bears: We Love Soccer [3 copies] (Box 309, Folder 1)
    - Berenstain, Mike. The Berenstain Bears: We Love Soccer [3 copies] (Box 309, Folder 2)
    - Berenstain, Mike. The Berenstain Bears: We Love Soccer [3 copies] (Box 309, Folder 3)
    - Berenstain, Mike. The Berenstain Bears: We Love Soccer [3 copies] (Box 309, Folder 4)
    - Berenstain, Mike. The Berenstain Bears: We Love Soccer [3 copies] (Box 309, Folder 5)
    - Berenstain, Jan & Mike. The Berenstain Bears: We Love Trucks (Box 309, Folder 6)
    - Berenstain, Stan & Jan. Call Mr Mrs. (Box 309, Folder 7)
    - Berenstain, Stan & Jan. Call Mr Mrs. (Box 309, Folder 7)
    - Berenstain, Stan & Jan. Down A Sunny Dirt Road: An Autobiography (Box 309, Folder 8)
    - Berenstain, Stan & Jan. Etiquette and Other Stuff for Newlyweds (Box 309, Folder 9)
    - Berenstain, Stan & Jan. The Facts of Life for Grown-Ups (Box 309, Folder 10)
    - Berenstain, Stan & Jan. Have a Baby, My Wife Just Had a Cigar (Box 309, Folder 11)
    - Berenstain, Stan & Jan. How to Be a Carefree Book (Box 309, Folder 12)
    - Berenstain, Stan & Jan. How to be Perfectly Yummy: Fabulous Fashion and Beauty Hints (Box 309, Folder 13)
    - Berenstain, Stan & Jan. How to Care for the Shiny New Baby (Box 309, Folder 14)
    - Berenstain, Stan & Jan. How to Fix-It Again and Again and Again (Box 309, Folder 15)
    - Berenstain, Stan & Jan. How to Have a Happy Anniversary (Box 309, Folder 16)
    - Berenstain, Stan & Jan. How to Have a Happy Birthday (Box 309, Folder 17)
    - Berenstain, Stan & Jan. How to Get Along in the Hospital: Helpful Hints for Impatient Patients (Box 309, Folder 18)
    - Berenstain, Stan & Jan. How to Teach Your Children About God Without Actually Scaring Them Out of Their Wits (Box 309, Folder 19)
    - Berenstain, Stan & Jan. How to Teach Your Children About God Without Actually Scaring Them Out of Their Wits (Box 309, Folder 19)
    - Berenstain, Stan & Jan. How to Teach Your Children About Sex...Without Making a Complete Fool of Yourself [2 copies] (Box 309, Folder 20)
    - Berenstain, Stan & Jan. How to Teach Your Children About Sex...Without Making a Complete Fool of Yourself (Box 309, Folder 21)
    - Berenstain, Stan & Jan. How to Teach Your Children About Sex...Without Making a Complete Fool of Yourself (Box 309, Folder 21)
    - Berenstain, Stan & Jan. I Love You But Oh My Wife (Box 309, Folder 22)
    - Berenstain, Stan & Jan. I Love You But Oh My Wife (Box 309, Folder 22)
    - Berenstain, Stan & Jan. Inside, Outside, Upside Down (Box 309, Folder 23)
    - Berenstain, Stan & Jan. It's All in the Family (Box 309, Folder 24)
    - Berenstain, Stan & Jan. It's Still in the Family (Box 309, Folder 24)
    - Berenstain, Stan & Jan. Marital Blitz (Box 309, Folder 25)
    - Berenstain, Stan & Jan. Mr. Dirty vs. Mrs. Clean (Box 310, Folder 1)
    - Berenstain, Stan & Jan. Physical Fitness for Softies of All Ages (Box 310, Folder 2)
    - Berenstain, Stan & Jan. Slightly Better Bowling (Box 310, Folder 2)
    - Berenstain, Stan & Jan. Squaresville: The Teen's Guide to Adult Behavior; Flipsville: The Adult's Guide to Teen-Age Behavior [2 copies] (Box 310, Folder 3)
    - Berenstain, Stan & Jan. Squaresville: The Teen's Guide to Adult Behavior; Flipsville: The Adult's Guide to Teen-Age Behavior (Box 310, Folder 4)
    - Berenstain, Stan & Jan. What Dr. Freud Didn't Tell You (Box 310, Folder 5)
    - Berenstain, Stan & Jan. What Your Parents Never Yold You About Being a Mom or Dad [3 copies] (Box 310, Folder 6)
    - Berenstain, Stan & Jan. What Your Parents Never Yold You About Being a Mom or Dad (Box 310, Folder 7)
    - Berenstain, Leo. The Wind Monkey (Box 310, Folder 8)
    - Berman, Mitch. Time Capsule (Box 310, Folder 9)
    - Bernays, Anne. Growing Up Rich (Box 310, Folder 10)
    - Bernays, Anne. Growing Up Rich (Box 310, Folder 11)
    - Bernays, Anne. Short Pleasures (Box 310, Folder 12)
    - Bernstein, Jeremy. The Wildest Dreams of Kew (Box 310, Folder 13)
    - Birmingham, Stephen. "Our Crowd": The Great Jewish Families of New York (Box 310, Folder 14)
    - Blair Jr., Clay. The Archbishop (Box 310, Folder 15)
    - Blair Jr., Clay. The Atomic Submarine (Box 311, Folder 1)
    - Blair Jr., Clay. The Board Room (Box 311, Folder 2)
    - Blanchan, Neltje. Nature's Garden (Box 311, Folder 3)
    - Bledsoe, Jerry. The World's Number One, Flat-Out, All-Time Great, Stock Car Racing Book (Box 311, Folder 4)
    - Block, Herbert. The Herblock Gallery (Box 311, Folder 5)
    - Bluestone, George. The Private World of Cully Powers (Box 311, Folder 6)
    - Bluestone, George. The Send-off (Box 311, Folder 7)
    - Blythe, Sarah Ganz and Edward D Powers. Looking at Dada (Box 311, Folder 8)
    - Bolles, Richard Nelson. What Color is Your Parachute? (Box 311, Folder 9)
    - Bonanno, Rosalie. Mafia Marriage: My Story (Box 311, Folder 10)
    - Boston Women's Health Book Collective. Our Bodies, Ourselves: A Book By and For Women (Box 311, Folder 11)
    - Bowen, Elizabeth. The Death of the Heart (Box 311, Folder 12)
    - Bowen, Robert O. The New Professionals (Box 311, Folder 13)
    - Bowen, Robert O. Sidestreet (Box 312, Folder 1)
    - Bowen, Robert O. The Weight of the Cross (Box 312, Folder 2)
    - Boynton, Robert S. The New New Journalism (Box 312, Folder 3)
    - Braddle, Benjamin C. Conversations with Kennedy (Box 312, Folder 4)
    - Braddle, Benjamin C. Conversations with Kennedy (Box 312, Folder 5)
    - Braiker, Harriet B. Getting Up When You're Feeling Down: A Woman's Guide to Beating the Blues (Box 312, Folder 6)
    - Brenton, Myron. Friendship (Box 312, Folder 7)
    - Breslin, Jimmy and Schaap, Dick. 0.44 (Box 312, Folder 8)
    - Breslin, Jimmy. He Got Hungry and Forgot His Manners (Box 312, Folder 9)
    - Breslin, Jimmy. Table Money (Box 312, Folder 10)
    - Brinkley, William. Breakpoint (Box 312, Folder 11)
    - Brinkley, William. Breakpoint (Box 312, Folder 12)
    - Brinkley, William. Don't Go Near the Water (Box 312, Folder 13)
    - Brinkely, William. Don't Go Near the Water (Box 313, Folder 1)
    - Brinkley, William. The Ninety and Nine (Box 313, Folder 2)
    - Brinkley, William. Peeper: A Comedy (Box 313, Folder 3)
    - Brinkley, William. Peeper: A Comedy (Box 313, Folder 4)
    - Brodeur, Paul. Currents of Death: Power Lines, Computer Terminals, and the Attempt to Cover Up Their Threat to Your Health (Box 313, Folder 5)
    - Brodeur, Paul. Downstream (Box 313, Folder 6)
    - Brodeur, Paul. Outrageous Misconduct: The Asbestors Industry on Trial (Box 313, Folder 7)
    - Brodeur, Paul. The Stunt Man (Box 313, Folder 8)
    - Brown, Allen. Golden Gate (Box 313, Folder 9)
    - Brown, Craig and Lesley Cunliffe. The Book of Royal Lists (Box 313, Folder 10)
    - Brown, Dan. The Da Vinci Code (Box 313, Folder 11)
    - Browne, Gerald A. 11 Harrowhouse (Box 313, Folder 12)
    - Browne, Gerald A. Green Ice (Box 314, Folder 1)
    - Browne, Gerald A. Stone 588 (Box 314, Folder 2)
    - Brue, Alexia. Cathedrals of the Flesh: My search For the Perfect Bath (Box 314, Folder 3)
    - Brue, Alexia. Cathedrals of the Flesh: My search For the Perfect Bath (Box 314, Folder 4)
    - Bruno, Jerry and Jeff Greenfield. The Advance Man (Box 314, Folder 5)
    - Bruno, Jerry and Jeff Greenfield. The Advance Man: An Off-beat Look at What Really Happens in Political Campaigns (Box 314, Folder 6)
    - Buchwald, Art. Whose Rose Garden Is It Anyway? (Box 314, Folder 7)
    - Buckley, I. Thomas. Penikese: Island of Hope (Box 314, Folder 8)
    - Budge, Don. A Tennis Memoir (Box 314, Folder 9)
    - Burke, Michael. Outrageous Good Fortune (Box 314, Folder 10)
    - Burton, Jeffery F., Mary M. Farrell, Florence B. Lord, and Richard W. Lord. Confinemend and Ethnicity: An Overview of World War II Japanese American Relocation Sites (Box 314, Folder 11)
    - Cahill, Kevin M. Threads for a Tapestry (Box 314, Folder 12)
    - Calder, Nigel. Einstein's Universe (Box 314, Folder 13)
    - Califano, Jr., Joseph A. America's Health Care Revolution: Who Lives? Who Dies? Who Pays? (Box 314, Folder 14)
    - Califano Jr., Joseph A. America's Healthcare Revolution (Box 315, Folder 1)
    - Califinao Jr., Joseph A. Governing America: An Insider's Report from the White House and the Cabinet (Box 315, Folder 2)
    - Califinao Jr., Joseph A. A Presidential Nation (Box 315, Folder 3)
    - Califinao Jr., Joseph A. The Triumph & Tragedy of Lyndon Johnson (Box 315, Folder 4)
    - Califinao Jr., Joseph A. The Triumph & Tragedy of Lyndon Johnson (Box 315, Folder 5)
    - Canfield, Cass. The Publishing Experience (Box 315, Folder 6)
    - Canning, Peter. American Dreamers: The Wallaces and Reader's Digest: an Insider's Story (Box 315, Folder 7)
    - Caro, Robert A. The Years of Lyndon Johnson: Means of Ascent (Box 315, Folder 8)
    - Carr, William H.A. The du Ponts of Deleware: A Fantastic Dynasty (Box 315, Folder 9)
    - Carter, Mary Randolph. The Welcome Book (Box 315, Folder 10)
    - Cartwright, Gary. The Hundred Yard War (Box 315, Folder 11)
    - Cassady, Carolyn. Off the Road: My Years with Cassady, Kerouac, and Ginsberg (Box 315, Folder 12)
    - Cassady, Neal. Grace Beats Karma: Letters from Prison 1958-60 (Box 316, Folder 1)
    - Cassini, Oleg. In My Own Fashion (Box 316, Folder 2)
    - Cerami, Charles A. Jefferson's Great Gamble (Box 316, Folder 3)
    - Cerf, Bennet. At Random: The Reminiscences of Bennet Cerf (Box 316, Folder 4)
    - Chandarlapaty, Raj. The Beat Generation and Counterculture (Box 316, Folder 5)
    - Charters, Ann, Ed. A Bibliography of Works by Jack Kerouac 1939-1975 (Revised Edition) (Box 316, Folder 6)
    - Charters, Ann. Kerouac: A Biography (Box 316, Folder 7)
    - Charters, Ann. The Penguin Book of the Beats (Box 316, Folder 8)
    - Charters, Ann, Ed. The Portable Jack Kerouac (Box 316, Folder 9)
    - Charters, Ann and Ginsberg, Allen. Scenes Along the Road: Photographs of the Desolation of Angels (Box 316, Folder 10)
    - Chase, Edward T. Covering the Court (Box 316, Folder 11)
    - Child, Julia with Alex Prud'homme. My Life in France (Box 316, Folder 12)
    - Chopra, Deepak. Creating Health (Box 316, Folder 13)
    - Christopher, Warren. Chances of a Lifetime: A Memoir (Box 316, Folder 14)
    - Clarke, Gerald. Capote: a Biography (Box 317, Folder 1)
    - Cohen, Neville S. and Joseph L. Shapiro. Out of Sight Into Vision (Box 317, Folder 2)
    - Collier, James Lincoln. The Teddy Bear Habit: Or How I Became a Winner (Box 317, Folder 3)
    - Collier, James Lincoln. Why Does Everybody Think I'm Nutty? (Box 317, Folder 4)
    - Conot, Robert E. American Odyssey: A Unique History of America Told Through the Life of a Great City (Box 317, Folder 5)
    - Conot, Robert E. Justice At Nuremberg (Box 317, Folder 6)
    - Conot, Robert E. Justice at Nuremberg: The First Comprehensive Dramatic Account of the Trial of the Nazi Leaders (Box 317, Folder 7)
    - Conot, Robert E. Rivers of Blood, Years of Darkness (Box 317, Folder 8)
    - Conot, Robert E. A Streak of Luck: The Life & Legend of Thomas Alva Edison (Box 317, Folder 9)
    - Conot, Robert E. Thomas Edison: A Streak of Luck (Box 317, Folder 10)
    - Conover, Ted. Rolling Nowhere (Box 318, Folder 1)
    - Conover, Ted. Whiteout (Box 318, Folder 2)
    - Conrad, Joseph. Almayer's Folly: A Story of an Eastern River (Box 318, Folder 3)
    - Conroy, Pat. The Prince of Tides (Box 318, Folder 4)
    - Cooper, T. Lipshitz Six, or Two Angry Blonfes (Box 318, Folder 5)
    - Cope, Myron. The Game That Was (Box 318, Folder 6)
    - Cordery, Stacy A. Alice: Alice Roosevelt Longsworth from White House Princess to Washington Power Broker (Box 318, Folder 7)
    - Cordery, Stacy A. Alice: Alice Roosevelt Longsworth from White House Princess to Washington Power Broker (Box 318, Folder 8)
    - Cordery, Stacy A. Juliette Gordon Low: The Remarkable Founder of the Girl Scouts (Box 318, Folder 9)
    - Cordery, Stacy A. Juliette Gordon Low: The Remarkable Founder of the Girl Scouts (Box 318, Folder 10)
    - Cordery, Stacy A. Juliette Gordon Low: The Remarkable Founder of the Girl Scouts (Box 318, Folder 11)
    - Cordery, Stacy A. Juliette Gordon Low: The Remarkable Founder of the Girl Scouts (Box 319, Folder 1)
    - Cordery, Stacy A. Juliette Gordon Low: The Remarkable Founder of the Girl Scouts (Box 319, Folder 2)
    - Cordery, Stacy A. Juliette Gordon Low: The Remarkable Founder of the Girl Scouts (Box 319, Folder 3)
    - Cordery, Stacy A. Juliette Gordon Low: The Remarkable Founder of the Girl Scouts (Box 319, Folder 4)
    - Cordery, Stacy A. Theodore Roosevelt: In The Vanguard of the Modern (Box 319, Folder 5)
    - Corricelli, Llord L. and and David Daniel. River Muse (Box 319, Folder 6)
    - Corry, John. Golden Clan (Box 319, Folder 7)
    - Corso, Gregory. An Accidental Autobiography (Box 319, Folder 8)
    - Corson, William R., Susan B. Trento, and Joseph J. Trento. Widows (Box 319, Folder 9)
    - Cox, Harvey. Just As I Am (Box 319, Folder 10)
    - Cox, Harvey. Religion in the Secular City: Toward a Postmodern Theology (Box 319, Folder 11)
    - Cox, Harvey. The Silencing of Leonardo Boff (Box 319, Folder 12)
    - Cramer, Richard Ben. How Israel Lost: The Four Questions (Box 319, Folder 13)
    - Cramer, Richard Ben. What It Takes: The Way to the White House (Box 320, Folder 1)
    - Creamer, Robert W. Babe: The Legend Comes to Life (Box 320, Folder 2)
    - Creamer, Robert W. Baseball and Other Matters in 1941 (Box 320, Folder 3)
    - Creamer, Robert W. Stengel: His Life and Times (Box 320, Folder 4)
    - Creamer, Robert W. Stengel: His Life and Times (Box 320, Folder 5)
    - Creamer, Robert W. Stengel: His Life and Times (Box 320, Folder 6)
    - Critchfield, Richard. Shahhat: An Egyptian (Box 320, Folder 7)
    - Critchfield, Richard. Those Days: An American Album (Box 320, Folder 8)
    - Critchfield, Richard. The Villagers: Changed Values, Altered Lives: The Closing of the Urban-Rural Gap (Box 320, Folder 9)
    - Crosette, Barbara. So Close to Heaven: The Vanishing Buddhist Kingdoms of the Himalayas (Box 320, Folder 10)
    - Crosette, Barbara. The Great Hill Stations of Asia (Box 320, Folder 11)
    - Crowley, Steve. Money for Life (Box 320, Folder 12)
    - Crystal, Billy. 700 Sundays (Box 320, Folder 12)
    - Cummings Jr., Milton and David Wise. Democracy Under Pressure: An Introduction to the American Political System (Box 321, Folder 1)
    - Cummings, Milton C., Jr. Democracy Under Pressure: An Introduction to the American Political System (Box 321, Folder 2)
    - Cummings Jr., Milton and David Wise. Democracy Under Pressure: An Introduction to the American Political System, Fifth Edition (Box 321, Folder 3)
    - Cunningham, E.V. An Assassin Who Gave Up His Gun (Box 321, Folder 4)
    - Cunningham, E.V. Alice (Box 321, Folder 4)
    - Cunningham, E.V. The Case of the Kidnapped Angel (Box 321, Folder 5)
    - Cunningham, E.V. The Case of the Kidnapped Angel (Box 321, Folder 5)
    - Cunningham, E.V. The Case of the Murdered Mackenzie (Box 321, Folder 6)
    - Cunningham, E.V. The Case of the Murdered Mackenzie (Box 321, Folder 6)
    - Cunningham, E.V. The Case of the Poisoned Eclairs (Box 321, Folder 7)
    - Cunningham, E.V. The Case of the Sliding Pool (Box 321, Folder 7)
    - Cunningham, E.V. The Case of the Sliding Pool (Box 321, Folder 8)
    - Cunningham, E.V. Cynthia (Box 321, Folder 8)
    - Cunningham, E.V. Margie (Box 321, Folder 9)
    - Cunningham, E.V. Helen (Box 321, Folder 9)
    - Cunningham, E.V. Phyllis (Box 321, Folder 10)
    - Cunningham, E.V. Sally (Box 322, Folder 1)
    - Cunningham, E.V. Samantha (Box 322, Folder 1)
    - Cunningham, E.V. Sylvia (Box 322, Folder 1)
    - Cunningham, E.V. Sylvia (Box 322, Folder 2)
    - Cunningham, E.V. The Wabash Factor (Box 322, Folder 3)
    - Cunningham, E.V. The Wabash Factor (Box 322, Folder 4)
    - Daley, Robert. Man With a Gun (Box 322, Folder 5)